Finding Aid for Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records
Clarke Historical Library
- Luedtke Engineering Company (Frankfort, Mich.) Organizational Records.
  - Daily Report, Job 701, 3 of 4,1990 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Daily Report, Job 701, 4 of 4,1990 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Daily Report, Job 702, 1 of 3,1990 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 702, 2 of 3,1990 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 702, 3 of 3,1990 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 703,1991 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 704,1991 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 705,1990 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 705,1991 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 705,1992 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 706, 1 of 3,1991 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 705, 2 of 3,1991 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 705, 3 of 3,1991 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 707, 1 of 3,1991 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Daily Report, Job 707, 2 of 3,1991 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Daily Report, Job 707, 3 of 3,1991 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 708, 1 of 2,1991 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 708, 2 of 2,1991 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 709, 1 of 5,1991 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 709, 2 of 5,1991 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 709, 3 of 5,1991 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 709, 4 of 5,1991 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 709, 5 of 5,1991 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 709-2, 1 of 4,1992 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 709-2, 2 of 4,1992 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 709-2, 3 of 4,1992 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 709-2, 4 of 4,1992 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Daily Report, Job 710,1991 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Daily Report, Job 711,1991 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Daily Report, Job 713, 1 of 4,1991 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Daily Report, Job 713, 2 of 4,1991 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, Job 713, 3 of 4,1991 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Daily Report, Job 713, 4 of 4,1991 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Job 5, Waukegan, IL,1932 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Job 6, Frankfort,1932 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Job 7, Algoma, WI,1932 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Job 8, Frankfort,1932 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Job 9, Algoma, WI,1932 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Job 10, 11, 12, Frankfort,1932 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Job 13, Frankfort,1933 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Job 14, Manistee,1933 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Job 15, Manistee,1933 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Job 16, Manistee,1933 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Job 17, Traverse City,1933 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Job 18, Manistee,1933 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Job 19, Frankfort,1933 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Job 20, Frankfort,1933 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Job 21, Frankfort,1934 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Job 22, Frankfort,1934 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Job 23, Rodal’s Tug, (no location),1934 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Job 24, Detroit,1934 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Job 25, Escanaba,1934-1935 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Job 25, Escanaba, photograph,undated (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Job 26, Port Huron,1935 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Job 26, Port Huron, Drawings,1935 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Job 27, Kewaunee, WI,1935 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Job 27, Kewaunee, WI, Drawings,1935 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Job 27, Kewaunee, WI, Photographs,1935 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Job 27A, Kewaunee, WI,1936 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Job 27B, Kewaunee, WI,1936 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Job 27C, Kewaunee, WI,1936 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Job 28, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1935 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Job 29, Kewaunee, WI,1936 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Job 30, Unknown location,1937-1938 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Job 31, Kewaunee, WI,1937 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Job 31, Kewaunee, WI, Drawings,1937 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Job 32, Frankfort,1937 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Job 33, Kewaunee, WI,1937-1938 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Job 34, Kewaunee, WI,1937 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Job 35, Frankfort,1937 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Job 35 A-B, Frankfort,1938 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Job 36, Mackinaw City,1937-1938 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Job 36, Mackinaw City, Drawings,1937-1938 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Job 37, Crystal Lake,1939 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Job 38, Menominee,1938 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Job 38, Menominee, Drawings,1938 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Job 39, Ludington,1939 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Job 40, Escanaba,1938 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Job 41, Straits of Mackinac,1938 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Job 41, Straits of Mackinac, Drawings,1938 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Job 41, Straits of Mackinac,1939 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Job 41, Straits of Mackinac, Blueprints,1939 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Job 41, Straits of Mackinac, Causeway,1949 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Job 41, Straits of Mackinac, Core Borings,1953 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Job 41, Straits of Mackinac, Reports,1939-1940 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Job 41, Straits of Mackinac, Rock Cores and Probes,1954 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Job 41, Straits of Mackinac, Tentative St. Ignace Plan,undated (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Job 41, Straits of Mackinac, Traffic Studies,1961 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Job 42, Washington Island, WI,1938-1939 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Job 42, Washington Island, WI,1940 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Job 42, Washington Island, WI, Correspondence with Congress,1940-1941 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Job 42, Washington Island, WI, Drawings,1938-1939 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Job 42, Washington Island, WI, Photographs,1939 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Job 43, Cheboygan,1939-1940 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Job 44, Kewaunee, WI,1939 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Job 45, St. Ignace,1939 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Job 46, Traverse City,1939 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Job 47, Charlevoix,1939 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Job 48, Frankfort,1939 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Job 49, New York, NY,1939 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Job 50, St. Ignace,1939 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Job 51, Frankfort,1939 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Job 52, Mackinac Island,1939 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Job 53, Frankfort,1939 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Job 54, Mackinaw City,1939-1940 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Job 55, Mackinac Island,1939-1940 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Job 56, Crystal Lake,1940 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Job 57, Muskegon Heights,1940-1941 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Job 57, Muskegon Heights, Drawings,1940 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Job 57, Muskegon Heights, Notice to Contractors, 1940 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Job 58, St. Ignace,1940 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Job 59, Frankfort,1940 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Job 60, St. Ignace,1940 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Job 61, Menominee, 1940 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Job 62, St. Joseph,1940 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Job 63, Frankfort,1940-1941 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Job 64, Frankfort,1940-1941 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Job 65, Frankfort,1940 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Job 66, Manistee,1940 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Job 67, Manistee,1940-1941 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Job 68, Frankfort,1941 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Job 69, Grand Haven,1941 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Job 70, Grand Rapids, 1 of 2,1941 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Job 70, Grand Rapids, 2 of 2,1941 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Job 70, Grand Rapids, Drawings,1938-1941 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Job 70, Grand Rapids, Newspaper clippings,1941 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Job 70A, Grand Rapids,1941 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Job 71, Ludington,1941 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Job 72, Ludington,1941 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Job 73, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1941 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Job 74, Ludington,1941 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Job 75, Ludington,1941 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Job 76, Sturgeon Bay, WI, 1 of 2,1942 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Job 76, Sturgeon Bay, WI, 2 of 2,1942 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Job 73, Sturgeon Bay, WI, Drawings,1942 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Job 77, Straits Causeway, 1 of 2,1941-1942 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Job 77, Straits Causeway, 2 of 2,1941-1942 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Job 77, Straits Causeway, Drawings, 1 of 2,1941-1942 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Job 77, Straits Causeway, Drawings, 2 of 2,1941-1942 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Job 78, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1941-1942 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Job 79, Mackinaw,1942 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Job 80, Frankfort,1942 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Job 81, Frankfort,1942 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Job 82, Frankfort,1942 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Job 83, Grand Rapids,1942 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Job 84, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1942 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Job 85, Frankfort,1942 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Job 86, Mackinac Island,1942 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Job 87, Mackinac Island,1942 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Job 88, Frankfort,1942 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Job 89, St. Ignace,1942 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Job 90, Frankfort,1943 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Job 91 – 91A, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1943 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Job 91B, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1944 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Job 92, Frankfort,1943 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Job 93, Mackinac Island,1943 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Job 94, Marinette, WI,1943 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Job 95, Frankfort,1943 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Job 96, Cheboygan,1943 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Job 98, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1943 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Job 99, Manistique,1944 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Job 100, Mackinaw city,1943 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Job H, Mackinaw city,1943-1944 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Job 101, Milwaukee, WI,1943-1944 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Job 102, Manitowoc, WI,1943-1944 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Job 103, North Manitou Island,1943 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Job 104, Frankfort,1943 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Job 105, Mackinaw,1943 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Job 106, Manistique,1943 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Job 107, Manistee,1943 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Job 108, Frankfort,1943-1944 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Job 109, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1944 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Job 110, Grand Haven,1944 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Job 111, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1944 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Job 112, Manistique,1944 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Job 113, Menominee Harbor,1944 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Job 114, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1944 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Job 115 – 115A, Frankfort,1944 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Job 116, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1944 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Job 117, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1944 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Job 118, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1944 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Job 119, Manistique,1944 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Job 120, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1944 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Job 121, Green Bay, WI,1944 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Job 122, St. Ignace and Mackinaw,1944 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Job 123, Menominee,1944 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Job 124, Frankfort,1944 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Job 125, Mackinaw,1944 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Job 125, Mackinaw, Drawings,1944 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Job 126, Kewaunee, WI,1945 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Job 127, Sturgeon Bay, WI, ,1945 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Job 128, Sturgeon Bay, WI, ,1945 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Job 129, Mackinac Island,1945 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Job 130, Mackinac Island,1945 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Job 131, Kewaunee, WI,1945 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Job 132, Mackinaw City,1945 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Job 133, Frankfort,1945 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Job 134, Kewaunee, WI,1945 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Job 134, Kewaunee, WI, Drawings,1945 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Job 135, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1945 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Job 136, Mackinac Island,1945 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Job 137, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1945 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Job 138, Mackinaw City,1945 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Job 138A, Mackinaw City,1945 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Job 138B, Mackinaw City,1946 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Job 138C, Mackinaw City,1946-1947 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Job 138D, Mackinaw City,1947 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Job 139, Frankfort,1945 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Job 140, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1945 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Job 141, St. Ignace,1945 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Job 142, Escanaba,1945 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Job 143, Bay City,1945 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Job 144, Menominee,1945 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Job 145, Milwaukee, WI,1945 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Job 146, St. Ignace,1945 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Job 147, St. Ignace,1946 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - JJob 148, Frankfort,1946 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Job 149, Round Island, 1 of 2,1946 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Job 149, Round Island, 2 of 2,1946 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Job 149, Round Island,1946-1947 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Job 149, Round Island,1947 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Job 149, Round Island, Drawings,1946 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Job 150, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1946 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Job 151, Frankfort,1946 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Job 152, Manitou Island,1946 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Job 153, Owosso,1946 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Job 154, Lansing,1946 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Job 155, Round Island,1946 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Job 156, Manistique,1946 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Job 157, Mackinac Island,1946 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Job 158, Albion,1946 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Job 159, Frankfort,1946-1947 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Job 160, St. Ignace,1946 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Job 161, Mackinac Island,1946 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Job 162, Charlevoix, 1 of 4,1947 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Job 162, Charlevoix, 2 of 4,1947 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Job 162, Charlevoix, 3 of 4,1947 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Job 162, Charlevoix, 4 of 4,1947 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Job 162, Charlevoix,1950 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Job 162, Charlevoix, Blue-line Drawings,1947 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Job 162, Charlevoix, Blueprints,1947 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Job 162, Charlevoix, Contract,1947 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Job 162, Charlevoix, Drawings,1947 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Job 162, Charlevoix, Photographs,1947 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Job 163, Charlevoix,1947 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Job 163, Charlevoix, Drawings,1947 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Job 164, Frankfort,1947 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Job 165, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1947 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Job 166, Drummond Island,1947 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Job 167, Mackinac Island,1947 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Job 168, St. Ignace,1947 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Job 169, St. Ignace,1947 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Job 170, St. Joseph,1947 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Job 171, Manistique,1947 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Job 172, Charlevoix,1947 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Job 173, Frankfort,1948 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Job 173, Frankfort, Drawings,1948 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Job 174, Frankfort,1947 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Job 175, St. Joseph,1948 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Job 176, Spring Lake,1948 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Job 176, Spring Lake, Blueprints,1948 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Job 176, Spring Lake, Photographs,1948 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Job 177, St. Ignace,1948 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Job 178, St. Ignace,1948 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Job 179, Mackinaw City,1948 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Job 180, Frankfort,1948 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Job 181, Frankfort,1948 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Job 182, Charlevoix,1948 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Job 182, Charlevoix, Drawings,1948 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Job 183, Mackinaw City,1948 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Job 183, Mackinaw City, Drawings,1948 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Job 184, Mackinaw City,1948 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Job 185, Mackinaw City,1948 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Job 186, Frankfort,1948 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Job 187, St. Ignace,1948 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Job 188, Frankfort,1949 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Job 189, Mackinaw City,1949 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Job 190, Benton Harbor, 1 of 3,1949-1950 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Job 190, Benton Harbor, 2 of 3,1949-1950 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Job 190, Benton Harbor, 3 of 3,1949-1950 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Job 190, Benton Harbor, Contract and Documents,1949-1950 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Job 190, Benton Harbor, Blue – line Drawings,1946-1949 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Job 190, Benton Harbor, Drawings,1949-1950 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Job 190, Benton Harbor, Drawings,1950 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Job 191, Frankfort,1949 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Job 192, Frankfort,1949 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Job 193, Frankfort,1949 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Job 195, Gulliver,1949 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Job 195, Kewaunee, WI,1949-1950 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Job 196, Waukegan, WI,1949 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Job 197, St. Ignace,1949 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Job 198, St. Ignace,1949 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Job Unknown, Port Washington, WI,1950 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Job 199, Frankfort,1949 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Job 200, Frankfort,1950 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Job 201, Frankfort,1950 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Job 202, Frankfort,1950 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Job 203, St. Ignace,1950 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Job 204, Sheboygan, WI, 1 of 3,1950 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Job 204, Sheboygan, WI, 2 of 3,1950 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Job 204, Sheboygan, WI, 3 of 3,1950 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Job 204, Sheboygan, WI, Blueprints,1950 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Job 204, Sheboygan, WI, Drawings,1950 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Job 205, Frankfort,1950 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Job 206, Frankfort,1950 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Job 207, Frankfort,1950 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Job 208, St. Ignace, 1 of 2,1950 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Job 208, St. Ignace, 2 of 2,1950 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Job 208, St. Ignace, Blueprints, 1 of 2,1950 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Job 208, St. Ignace, Blueprints, 2 of 2,1950 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Job 208, St. Ignace, Blue – line Drawings,1950 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Job 209, Mackinaw City,1950 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Job 210, Detour,1950 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Job 211, Mackinaw City,1951 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Job 211, Mackinaw City, Drawings,1951 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Job 212, Frankfort,1951 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Job 213, Mackinaw City,1950 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Job 213, Mackinaw City, Drawings,1950 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Job 214, St. Ignace,1950 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Job 215, St. Ignace,1951 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Job 216, Frankfort,1951 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Job 217, Mackinac Island,1951 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Job 218, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1951 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Job 219A, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1951 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Job 219B, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1952 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Job 220, Port Inland,1951 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Job 221, Drummond Island,1951 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Job 221, Drummond Island, Drawings,1951 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Job 222, Elberta,1951 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Job 223, and A – B, Manistique,1951-1952 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Job 224A, Sault Ste. Marie,1951 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Job 224A, Sault Ste. Marie, Contract,1951 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Job 224A, Sault Ste. Marie, Drawings,1951 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Job 225, Sault Ste. Marie, Drawings,1951 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Job 226, St. Ignace,1951 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Job 227, Elberta,1952 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Job 228, Drummond Island,1952 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Job 229, Manistique,1952 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Job 230, St. Ignace,1952 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Job 231, Mackinac Island,1952 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Job 232, Mackinaw City,1952 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Job 233, Frechette Point,1952 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Job 234, Gulliver,1952 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Job 235, Frankfort,1952-1953 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Job 236, Sault Ste. Marie,1952 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Job 237, Manistique,1952-1953 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Job 238, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1953 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Job 239, Elberta,1953 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Job 240, Sault Ste. Marie,1953 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Job 240, Sault Ste. Marie, Drawings,1953 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Job 240, Sault Ste. Marie, Photographs,1953 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Job 241, Sault Ste. Marie,1953 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Job 241, Sault Ste. Marie, Photographs,1953 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Job 242, Drummond Island,1953 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Job 243, Mackinac Island,1953 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Job 244, Frankfort,1953 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Job 245, Grand Haven,1953-1955 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Job 245, Grand Haven, Drawings,1953 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Job 245, Grand Haven, Invoices,1953 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Job 245, Grand Haven, Specifications,1953 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Job 246 Sault Ste. Marie, CA,1953 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Job 247, St. Ignace,1953 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Job 248, St. Ignace,1953 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Job 249, St. Ignace,1953 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Job 250, St. Ignace,1953 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Job 251, St. Ignace,1953 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Job 252, Mackinac Island,1953 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Job 253, Drummond Island, ,1953-1954 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Job 254, Elberta,1954 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Job 255, Frankfort, 1 of 2,1954 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Job 255, Frankfort, 2 of 2,1954 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Job 256, Grand Haven,1954-1955 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Job 256, Grand Haven, Blue – line Drawings,1953 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Job 256, Grand Haven, Contract,1954 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Job 256, Grand Haven, Estimates,1954 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Job 256, Grand Haven, Invoices,1954 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Job 257, Sturgeon Bay, WI,1954-1955 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Job 257, Sturgeon Bay, WI, Contract and Drawings,1954 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Job 257, Sturgeon Bay, WI, Photographs,1954 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Job 258, Muskegon,1954 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Job 259, Ludington,1954 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Job 260, Elberta,1954 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Job 261, Holland, 1 of 3,1955 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Job 261, Holland, 2 of 3,1955 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Job 261, Holland, 3 of 3,1955 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Job 261, Holland, Blue – line Drawings, 1 of 3,1955 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Job 261, Holland, Blue – line Drawings, 2 of 3,1955 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Job 261, Holland, Blue – line Drawings, 3 of 3,1955 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Job 262, Frankfort,1955 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Job 263, Elberta,1955 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Job 264, Gulliver,1955 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Job 265, Gulliver,1955 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Job 266, Elberta,1955 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Job 267, Mackinac Island,1955 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Job 268, Mackinac Island,1955 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Job 269, Mackinac City,1955 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Job 271, St. Ignace,1955 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Job 272, Drummond Island,1955 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Job 272, Drummond Island, Blue – line Drawings,1955 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Job 272, Drummond Island, Drawings,1955 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Job 273, Mackinaw City,1955 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Job 274, Detour,1955 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Job 274, Detour, Drawings,1955 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Job 275, Mackinaw City,1955 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Job 276, Elberta,1955 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Job 277, Frankfort,1956 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Job 278, Elberta,1956 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Job 279, Frankfort,1956 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Job 280, Chicago, IL, 1 of 2,1956-1957 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Job 280, Chicago, IL, 2 of 2,1956-1957 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Job 280, Chicago, IL, Drawings,1956 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Job 281, Mackinac Island,1956 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Job 282, Port Huron, 1 of 4,1956 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Job 282, Port Huron, 2 of 4,1956 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Job 282, Port Huron, 3 of 4,1956 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Job 282, Port Huron, 4 of 4,1956 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Job 282, Port Huron, Drawings, 1 of 2,1956 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Job 282, Port Huron, Drawings, 2 of 2,1956 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Job 282, Port Huron, Instructions to Bidders and Agreement,1956 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Job 283, Frankfort,1956-1957 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Job 284, St. Ignace,1956 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Job 285, Frankfort,1957 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Job 286, Manistee,1957 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Job 286, Manistee, Blueprints,1956 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Job 286, Manistee, Drawings,1956 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Job 287, Port Huron,1957 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Job 288, Frankfort,1957 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Job 289, Ludington Harbor, 1 of 2,1957 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Job 289, Ludington Harbor, 2 of 2,1957 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Job 289, Ludington Harbor, Blueprints,1957 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Job 289, Ludington Harbor, Blue – line Drawings,1957 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Job 290, Frankfort,1957 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Job 291, Frankfort,1957 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Job 292, Frankfort,1957 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Job 293, Frankfort,1957 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Job 294, Frankfort,1958 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Job 295, Kenosha, WI,1958 (Box 108, Folder 12)